torrentavi.com 2011-09-22

# Privacy Policy | Torrent Avi, Movie Releases, Torrent Movies

## Privacy Policy

**Torrent AVI values your privacy. We will never disclose your personal information (email address, IP addresses, etc.) and associated activity on this Web site to any third party, without your permission. We also will not retain your personal information for any longer than necessary for administrative purposes. Our google analytics collects cookies and other info while you browse the site. More specifically the DoubleClick DART cookie is used by Google in the adsense ads served on this website.**

**IP Addresses**

An IP (Internet Protocol) address is a set of numbers assigned to you by your ISP (Internet Service Provider) during the time that you are online. Every website you visit has access to this information, due to the way the Internet works. This is nothing to worry about, as all websites need your IP in order to discern where they have to send the information to.

We (Torrent AVI) only record IP addresses for the usage of statistics and when users enter comments on the website.

**Email Addresses**

We require proper and correct email addresses for an leaving a user comment due to security reasons, and once provided, it is kept on file to link your email address to your account name. This information never leaves the boundaries of the site’s database, and you can be assured that only you and the staff have access to that information.

**External Links**

Within the site, various external links may be present to sites that we do not own, and therefore have no control over. We do not necessarily admonish or support the privacy practices of these sites, and cannot be held responsible for neither the content, nor the privacy practices. We urge you to be careful when clicking on external URLs, and if you do find an uncrupulous link upon the site, feel free to report your findings to us, and we will deem whether it is necessary to remove the link.

**Public Forums**

We may or may not provide message boards and comments systems to our members and the general public. Please remember that any information within these areas is considered public, and you should therefore exercise caution when deciding to disclose any personal information. In fact, we highly frown on such practices that are not within private boundaries. We cannot be held responsible for protecting the privacy of any information that you willingly choose to disclose upon the site. You do so at your own risk.

**Security**

One thing we are proud of is our dedication to site security, and doing as much as physically possible to protect your personal information from loss, misuse, unauthorised access or alteration. Please bear in mind that we cannot guarantee under all circumstances that loss, misuse, unauthorised access or alteration to data will never occur. Therefore, we will not be held responsible should any of the aforementioned occur.
